How's it feel to to be here? I know it
kind of got out there a couple days ago,
but to finally get it official and
everything, how's that feel?
>> No, I'm juiced, man. Super excited. Uh,
you know, I think, you know, you know,
God kind of works in mysterious ways
because I bought a house out here last
year in Gilbert and then got out here
about a month and a half ago and now now
I'm here, you know, year round. So, I'm
I'm super happy.
>> Why did you choose to get a house out
here? Uh, I've visited out here a bunch.
My, uh, dad used to coach at UOVA and
ASU for a year and, uh, I just, I mean,
I love the area. I love being back on
the West Coast, uh, closer to family
and, uh, yeah, I'm just super excited to
get to work.
>> How much of a factor was that that you
have now a place to call home?
>> Yeah. Uh, it it was definitely a part of
it. You know, I think for me though, you
know, football always comes first and,
you know, getting the chance to, you
know, work with uh, you know, the new
head coach and coach Rafur and also, you
know, be in our old line room that I
think, you know, is is starting to to
rebuild and, um, you know, I just want
to and honestly too like uh, you know,
the GM and those guys wanted me here and
you know, it's great to be at a place
that you wanted.
You mentioned the, you know, a team
that's kind of rebuilding a little bit
at this stage in your career. Why did
you want to be a part of something like
that?
>> You know, I I enjoyed the process. You
know, I think at this point in my
career, if you don't enjoy those other,
you know, five, six days, then um you're
going to have a really miserable
experience. and uh the process of like
putting together a game plan, you know,
schematics, technical work, uh how can I
get better every day, how can I help my
teammates every day, that's always at
the forefront of my mind. And uh
ultimately, you know, if you love the
process, you know, wins usually come. Um
but, you know, I'm a very
processoriented person and you know,
this is some somewhere and something I
want to be a part of. for fans who might
not be super familiar with your your
Dame, how would you kind of describe
what you're going to bring to this
organization?
>> Yeah, I think um you know, a lot of
people might hear or mention like
leadership and um the mentality and you
know, you know, first and foremost, I
want to be my goal is to be the best at
what I do at my position. Um the
perfection is not something you can get,
but the pursuit of perfection is
something that I always strive for. Uh,
like I said before, like how can I
constantly improve? Uh, I want to come
in with a um, you know, like a sponge
and know that I don't have all the
answers, but I'm always here to learn.
You know, I want the O line room to be a
collaborative effort with Coach Fry and
Coach Cook. Um, and you know, I want
guys to to feel like they come in every
day and enjoy where they work and not
only enjoy, but also try to squeeze as
much as you can out of each and every
day. And um you know the the the goal is
as a unit to be great at what we do.
>> By all the advanced metrics, you've been
at your best over this past couple
seasons. Um and and really performing at
an elite level. What is it about kind of
your development as a player that's
enabled you to kind of hit this stride
over these past couple seasons?
>> Yeah, I think as you get older, you
know, you evolve not only your game, but
uh you know, the other uh part of it is
what are you doing off the field? How
are you eating? Do you get enough rest?
Are you doing you know whatever?
Mobility, flexibility, strength work,
PT,
uh stem cell is a big thing now. Like I
will scour every part of the planet to
get whatever I possibly can to get an
advantage over everybody else. Uh, I
truly believe that regardless if you're
a 11-year vet on a multi-year contract
or a rookie, undrafted rookie, we are
all held at the same standard and
everybody's constantly competing every
single day. Um, so I doesn't matter if I
if you're a pro bowler or unproven, you
know, you got to prove it every single
day at practice, every single game. And,
uh, that's the mindset I have.
>> Is that a mindset that has grown for you
over the years? Is that something that
your your father helped instill in you
or did you need to get to that place
personally before you really
>> It's always a uh you know adaptive
journey. Um I think I am extremely
thankful for the parents that I had that
instilled a very intrinsic motivation
for me to be great. Um and as you grow
you learn and adapt and talk with uh
I've you know older guys. I I especially
appreciate my time in Philly. Um, Jeff
Stoutland, shout out. Um, one of the
best coaches I ever played for and the
guys that I played there with were
extremely helpful and made me see the
game in a new lens. Pittsburgh gave me a
whole different perspective. Coach Pat
Meyer, another great coach. Um, and kind
of being an older guy there, learning
that dynamic. Uh, so I'm I I never want
to be the guy that thinks he has all the
answers because then you get put in a
box and you don't get any better and you
don't learn. So, uh, I want to be the
guy that's, you know, open to learning
and getting better and thinking outside
the box and, uh, just want to, you know,
be as great as I possibly can be and
then do everything I possibly can to
help my teammates.
>> How much do you know about Paris Johnson
as left tackle and then what goes into
kind of building a relationship with the
guy who's next to you?
>> Yeah, I mean, I I've obviously seen a
couple games just from watching film
last year, uh, when we were game
planning. Uh, I know he's a hell of a
player, a hell of a talent. You know,
came from Ohio State. You know, they
only put out really good players. So,
uh, I don't know much about him. You
know, I haven't spoken with him yet, but
I'm excited to, you know, build that
bond, you know, and honestly, that that
kind of thing just comes with time um on
and off the field really. Uh, but you
know, I I would hope that um, you know,
the the tape shows something to him and
because it show because his tape shows
something to me and uh, I'm just, you
know, juiced to to get to work.
>> As a guy in the in the locker room that
has a Super Bowl ring and has been there
and done that, how much do you put that
out there as just kind of like this is
what it takes to to get there, get the
job done?
>> Yeah, I mean it's it's tough. It's cool
to have I think really that you know
Super Bowl ring like 20 years from now
is going to be really cool deal that to
to think of. But in terms of football
and the season it's such a you know what
have you done for me lately? What are
you doing right now? Uh you could be you
know a hall of famer or you know allp
pro guy but you have one bad game man uh
you know that thing lingers because it's
the most freshest wound. Um so to me I
don't try to put anything like that out
there. I want guys to see how I am every
day. You know, the routine that I have,
the professionalism I have, the
mentality of wanting to be great and not
um, you know, believing that I know
everything or this or that. Um, so I I I
try to humble myself because the NFL
humbles people pretty often. So, you'd
rather come in with humility than try to
come in with a sense of know-it-all or
arrogance.
>> Thoughts of going up against Josh Schwe?
>> Say that again.
>> Thoughts about just going up against
Josh Sweat? Oh, Joshua's a dog. Um, I
mean, we knew I knew that in Philly and,
uh, seeing him blossom into like a
extremely good player, you know, it's
great. I'm great. I'm glad he's on our
team. Um, and that's the best part, you
know, the best part about football is
you you're not only, you know, uh,
trying to be the best in the world, but
you get to go up against the best guys
in the world. Um, and as they say, like
iron iron sharpens iron. Um, so I'm
Yeah, I'm excited about that.
Sweaty Jay back.
>> You lean more heavily Wildats or Suns
based on your [laughter]
>> you know right now I root for you know
Oregon State Beaver because that's where
my dad dad is. Um just so happens to be
my alumni as well. But that's my
loyalties always lie where um my
family's at. Uh my sister is a little a
little tough sometimes. You know it's
going to be tough. Uh, I I'll root for
her about the the 14 or 15 other weeks,
but unfortunately not those those two
times we play them.
>> Can you walk through your free agent
process? Like maybe when you knew the
Cardinals weren't [clears throat]
interested, like was it really a debate
with other teams? I guess the ultimate
question is like why did you want to be
here?
>> Yeah, I mean I'll be honest with you. I
mean money's good. Can't complain, you
know, that's I'm not going to pretend
that's not a part of it. But uh also
living, you know, already living out
here made a factor. But you know, the
biggest part is I want to win and I want
to win with a team that wants me here.
Um and I see that with coach. I see that
with you know, the group that we have,
the group that we're building. Um you
know, Cardinals reached out like the
same every other team reached out when
it was appropriate and you know, reached
out to my agent. Uh but it takes a lot
of factors but you know um at the end of
the day winning is the most important
important thing.
>> I don't know they my agent took care of
that. I was just busy training taking
care of my daughter.